# JAMES V. KEEFE, JR.

Dover, NH 03820 Open to Remote Work (603) 534-8506) jvkeefe@gmail.com www.github.com/jkeefe77

SUMMARY Former police officer turned web developer. Experienced in building customized web pages and applications for both web and mobile development. Active listener and effective communicator with analytical skills that allow for the design of responsive apps with the customer vision always in focus. Adaptable, focused, and capable of managing complex tasks to meet any deadline.

EDUCATION SUFFOLK UNIVERSITY Boston, MA

September 2003- April 2007

Bachelor of Arts, Sociology

**CAREER FOUNDRY** 

April 2023- present

Full Stack web developer certification (in progress)

## SKILLS CODING LANGUAGES / SPECIALTIES

- Full Stack web development (MERN)
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, SQL
- Git, GitHub, Git Bash, cloud computing.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **TOWN OF FARMINGTON** Farmington, NH

# CITY OF DOVER Dover, NH

April 2016 – March 2023

Police Officer

- Train and evaluate recruits as a Field Training Officer
- Conduct thorough investigations for various criminal offenses
- Process evidence as member of Crime Scene Unit

## PARADIGM PRECISION Malden, MA

March 2012 - April 2016

Material Coordinator/ Buyer

- Coordinate material movement between internal teams and outside suppliers
- Negotiate with suppliers for optimal pricing and conditions
- Managing costs as part of the procurement process with supply chain management